All right. So, uh, yes, approved.
Proceed
with part five. And off it goes. And
again, I'll see you in a sec. Okay, it
says now that part five is waiting for
the sign off. Part five, you may
remember, is all really about
documenting the database because you do
want to check this out first. So, I'm
going to open this. Let me close this.
Have a look at this. Uh, so the users is
a database table. That makes sense.
board, one board per user. Um, title
stored for future multiboard expansion.
That makes sense. Columns, cards. Okay.
Ordering strategy, migration approach.
So, it's interesting. It's I I had
thought it would store everything as a
JSON blob so it could be easily
provided, but this is possibly a better
design. I I'm maybe I mine was was not
perhaps the uh most sensible way of
doing it. This seems like a pretty good
approach, I have to say. Uh, so I'm
we're going to go with it. We are going
to say that that uh we're going to trust
that the AI has thought this one
through. We're going to approve.
Approved.
Proceed
to part six. I probably would have done
it differently, but then my way might
have been a little bit more hacky. This
is perhaps a better way of doing it. We
will see. I'll let it do part six and
I'll see you in a sec. Okay. Well, I
confirmed part six finished and then I
checked it. Nothing is broken. It hasn't
yet wired up the front end, the back
end. Everything still seems to be fine.
Again, I'm going to uh do a get status.
I'm going to do a git add get commit
minus m part 6 done.
Okay. Okay, so we've taken our git
checkpoint and now we come over here and
say proceed with
part seven. I'll also press keep here.
So we keep all those changes. Proceed
with part seven and off it goes. And we
will uh yeah, a moment ago I thought
that that it was already hooked up the
front end and back end. I forgot that
that's what part seven is all about.
Part seven is hooking up the front end
and the back end. That's what it's now
doing. It's a big deal. So this is
probably the most significant change
we've had so far. I will see you when
it's ready. Okay, it's been enthralling,
but it's been 15 minutes on the go here
and we are now at the point where I do
believe we have a part seven ready for
us to test and it's been a lot of
change. A lot has happened, a lot of
changes. Tests were repeatedly failing
and it rebuilt them. It had to do a lot
of rewriting of the front end for this
to work. So anyway, let's let's do the
usual um uh script start mac. Let it
come up. See if it does come up
successfully. It's building a production
build, which is what I like to see. This
is these are the the steps that it would
need to do. Okay. And it believes that
it's running. Let's go and take a look.
Here it is. Local host 8000. Okay. So
far so good. It's serving uh something
here. User and password. We'll get those
usual warnings. Here it comes. Okay.
Okay. Uh and uh not now. All right. So,
here we have it. Uh let's move this over
here.
Uh, well, that's not a good sign, is it?
Uh, that's interesting. That one did
move. There's something janky with the
way that they move. But anyway, let's
start by seeing if this has worked. So,
we've moved this over here. Let's bring
up a separate browser. Let's we'll
actually close that down al together.
Come in again. Log in as user password
and see what's happened there. And it
has indeed come up fine. It's moved it
to the second column. It did get
persisted. That's pretty impressive.
This is working nicely. We just have to
fix this uh this this problem with the
drag and drop. So, I'll I'll dig into
that a bit and then we'll give it a
message. Okay. So, I'm going to stop the
server. I'm going to do a get status.
I'm just going to make sure we capture
where we are. get add dot get commit
minus m part seven built some drag and
drop bugs.
Okay. And now I'm going to see if I
can't prompt it to fix these UI bugs.
The persistence is working, but the drag
and drop
seems to only work. Occasionally,
most of the time I drag a card,
the next column highlights,
but when I release
the card goes back to its original
position.
Please test thoroughly and fix
fix uh uh reproduce the problem
fix it and confirm it is fixed. That is
the way to do it. Always make sure that
you're very uh prescriptive about
debugging and we'll see how it gets on
with this. I will see you in a sec.
Okay, so this has been an interesting
debugging experience just trying to get
the drag and drop to work. It's been
going at it for half an hour. It's been
continually in this loop. It seems
really stuck in a rut of trying again
and again. And I can see it keeps saying
it's likely because of this. I keep
seeing it like jumping to conclusions,
which is such a such a classic move by
the LLM. And then somewhat to my
surprise, I stopped it. You can stop it
by pressing like the stop button that's
here. And I just decided to go in and
try it myself. And I found that it has
in fact fixed it along the way. At some
point in the last half an hour, it did
actually fix it. It's working great, but
the tests that it was running to try and
test drag and drop were failing. And so
it just continually decided that it
hadn't fixed it. So kind of bizarre, but
it it shows that that that human
involvement was needed to be able to
check and confirm that actually it's
working fine. So now with that in mind,
let me show you it working uh right now.
So I'm going to bring up my server with
startmac.shell.
Up it comes. Everything is starting up.
Go to a browser. Go to localhost 8000.
Here we go. We're going to go in as user
password. We're going to get that angry
message saying it's not a good password.
Yes. Yes, we know that. Here we are.
We're at a cambban studio. I can now
indeed drag and drop. And it works. And
there it is. And now we willh do some
more dragging. I'll drag that one over
there. Now this is empty. See all of
that. I'm going to open a new tab. I'm
going to close this tab down. I'm going
to go back to local host 8000. I'm going
to log in again as user and password and
sign in. And back we are. And you can
see that that has worked. We've got an
empty column here. Everything is looking
great. Congratulations to our our agent
to codeex. Things are going well. Okay.
So, back I go here. I'm going to stop
that server. I'm also going to do a get
status. Uh, and I'm going to do a get
add dot and get commit minus am
part seven working.
And there we've done it. We're in good
shape. We we uh now have uh uh part part
seven is in good shape. It's time for us
to move on. Let's just quickly take a
look at the plan to remind ourselves of
where we are here. Uh, part seven is
done and we're going on to part eight,
which is AI connectivity. And now I have
something important to discuss with you.
Over the course of this this uh time
that we've spent together going through
parts 1 to 7, our context window has
been gradually filling up. We don't
actually get that display that we get in
uh when we're using cursor. it's it's
handling it for us, but we know that
we're we're filling things up and we've
certainly reached a point now where it's
going to be summarizing and dropping
some of the messages and so on as we
this is something that that we are going
to obsess over when we use Claude Code
next week and and everyone that is that
is a pro on Claude Code obsesses over
this and and we don't have as much
visibility to it, but we should obsess
over it just as much nonetheless. And a
technique that is a common good
practice, but it feels kind of gling to
do it is that at some point we should
stop the chat and start again and have
it read plan.md to understand where
we've got. So that's what we're going to
do now. I'm going to start by saying uh
please confirm that plan. MD is up to
date with all the latest,
including
any design decisions that you made. Let
me know when ready. So, we're going to
update plan.mmd and make sure that that
we're super happy with it. And then
we're going to do a big step of
resetting the chat. Okay, that is done.
So, I'm going to press keep here to keep
the changes. I'm just going to do one
more get status and just just see it has
indeed updated the plan MD. I'm just
going to do a get add dot get commit as
m final uh tweaks uh final uh uh updates
after part seven.
And uh that is done. And here we go. And
what I'm now going to do is over here I
am going to rightclick here and I'm
going to say new chat. Starting all over
again. Build with agent. Here we go.
It's time for us to go on to part eight.